<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyVinnytsia</string>
    <string name="tab_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="tab_lodging">Lodging</string>
    <string name="tab_taste">Taste</string>

    <string name="place_0_location">Roshen embankment, Karmeliuka St.</string>
    <string name="place_0_name">Fountain on the Pivdennyi Buh</string>
    <string name="place_0_description">
        If you ask what to see in Vinnytsia, everyone will say without hesitation: first of all,
        the light and music fountain Roshen on the Pivdennyi Buh, which was inaugurated in 2011.
        It is currently the largest floating fountain in Europe. According to experts, it is also
        among the ten most spectacular fountains in the world. The vertical jet is 60 meters high
        and the frontal span is 140 meters. The use of a laser projector and a water-air screen
        allows the demonstration of video in 3D. During the day, jets of water create an effect
        of harmony and tranquility, and in the evening, a grand show begins: various multimedia
        masterpieces are shown in front of a large open-air auditorium on a giant water canvas.
        The combination of classical music, dance performances and vivid stories attracts people
        to admire the show and makes the fountain a symbol of the City of ideas. Each thematic
        program is not just an entertaining water show, but a real work of contemporary art and is
        designed for the general public, regardless of age, gender and preferences.
    </string>

    <string name="place_1_location">city center</string>
    <string name="place_1_name">European Square and Artynov Tower</string>
    <string name="place_1_description">
        The park around the square is located in the heart of the city and is one of the favorite
        places for recreation. It is here that the Artynov Water Tower, the main symbol of
        Vinnytsia and its business card, is located. At the beginning of the 20th century, the
        architect Hryhorii Artynov designed it as a water pumping station for the city water supply
        system and an observation tower of the fire-brigade. The clock was supposed to give it a
        town hall-like appearance. For more than a hundred years of existence, the tower has
        performed various functions and changed many residents. Currently, it is a home to the
        Museum of Vinnytsia. Young musicians often perform on European Square, themed locations are
        set up during festivals and celebrations, and walking in the park is a pleasure at any time
        of the year. The melody of the legendary Shchedryk (Carol of the Bells) by Leontovych,
        which made him famous all over the world, is heard from the tower.
</string>

    <string name="place_2_location">city center</string>
    <string name="place_2_name">Soborna Street</string>
    <string name="place_2_description">
        It was once called Mykolaivska Avenue, then Poshtova. Today it has an extremely elegant
        name — Soborna. At all times, the main artery of the city has been in the vortex of
        events. Decorated with monumental structures, majestic buildings of different historical
        eras, it attracts tourists from different countries. The author of many architectural
        masterpieces was the first city architect Hryhorii Artynov. The buildings of the City Duma
        and the women’s gymnasium, the elegant Savoy Hotel – the architect actually created the
        face of the city. Part of the street is paved with cobblestones, which also gives it a
        special, historic charm.
    </string>

    <string name="place_3_location">155 Pirogova St</string>
    <string name="place_3_name">National Pirogov`s Estate Museum</string>
    <string name="place_3_description">
        The main tourist attractions of the City of ideas are headed by the Pirogov Museum in
        Vinnytsia. When asked “What to see in Vinnytsia first?” every resident of Vinnytsia will
        confidently name this iconic place, along with the Mykhailo Kotsiubynskyi Museum-Estate,
        the legendary Vinnytsia Mures, or the Vinnytsia Catacombs. For a long time, Nikolai Pirogov
        was the center of the city’s life, settling in the picturesque Vyshnia estate. He was a
        world-renowned scientist, a brilliant surgeon, and a talented teacher whose achievements
        are hard to overestimate. It was here that the “Vinnytsia stage” of his life, which lasted
        more than 20 years, took place. To this day, grateful descendants visit the National
        Pirogov’s Estate Museum and the church-tomb of Pirogov, where his embalmed body lies.
        Tourists from all over the world come here! The museum and estate complex, dedicated to the
        life and work of the prominent surgeon, is located in a picturesque place near Vyshenske
        Lake. Today, it is not only a cultural landmark of Vinnytsia, but also one of the most
        popular tourist attractions in the city. Here you can delve into the life story of an
        extraordinary person, learn a lot of interesting things about an outstanding doctor,
        enjoy a walk in a cozy park and buy souvenirs. By the way, you can also buy nice little
        things to remember your trip and useful things in other parts of the city.
    </string>

    <string name="place_4_location">34 Soborna St</string>
    <string name="place_4_name">Hotel France</string>
    <string name="place_4_description">
        Address: 34 Soborna St.
        Phones:
        Reception: +380 68 055-88-88,
        Reservation Department: +380 63 552-92-11,
        Conference Service: +380 68 055-88-87.
        Website: hotelfrance.com.ua
        Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/hotelfranceua/
    </string>

    <string name="place_5_location">15 Khlibna St</string>
    <string name="place_5_name">Fenix Town</string>
    <string name="place_5_description">
        Address: 15 Khlibna St.
        Phone: +380 96 000-26-08
        Website: fenix-hotel.com.ua/hotel-fenix-town
        Instagram: https://is.gd/2NEKrV
    </string>

    <string name="place_6_location">57а Arkhitektora Artynova St</string>
    <string name="place_6_name">Smart Apart</string>
    <string name="place_6_description">
        Address: 57a, Arkhitektora Artynova St.
        Phone: +380 98 054-54-55
        Website: smartapart.net
        Social networks:
        Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/smartapart.vinnytsia/
        Instagram: https://is.gd/SJPICU
    </string>

    <string name="place_7_location">18 Yunosti Ave</string>
    <string name="place_7_name">Small Hotel</string>
    <string name="place_7_description">
        Address: Prospekt Yunosti, 18.
        Phone: +380 93 930-11-11
        Website: https://small-hotel.com.ua/
        Social networks:
        Facebook: Facebook.com/smalhotel
        Instagram: Instagram.com/small.hotel
    </string>

    <string name="place_8_location">8 Mykoly Ovodova St</string>
    <string name="place_8_name">Chernomorka restaurant</string>
    <string name="place_8_description">
        Shop-restaurant of the chain of the same name. The menu includes fish and seafood caught on
        our own pier in the village of Mykolaivka in the Odesa region.

        18 Mykoly Ovodova St
        +380 96 994-05-05
        https://www.instagram.com/chernomorka.vinnytsia
    </string>

    <string name="place_9_location">2 Karmeliuka St</string>
    <string name="place_9_name">Ostannie Kytaiske bistro</string>
    <string name="place_9_description">
        Vinnytsia bistro of Pan-Asian cuisine, which offers a wide range of Far Eastern dishes.
        Peking duck in a traditional serving, seafood and other delicacies of the Celestial Empire.

        2 Karmeliuka St
        +380 67 103-01-10
        https://lastchinese.choiceqr.com
        https://www.fb.com/lastchinese
    </string>

    <string name="place_10_location">121 Keletska St</string>
    <string name="place_10_name">Red Zeppelin restaurant</string>
    <string name="place_10_description">
        American cuisine and rock aesthetics, tables for large groups on the atmospheric terrace,
        appetizing dishes and a wide selection of different types of beers.

        121 Keletska St (Plaza Park Mall)
        +380 (97) 173-45-54,
        +380 (63) 589-44-95.

        https://facebook.com/zeppelinred/
        https://www.instagram.com/redzeppelin_vn/
    </string>

    <string name="place_11_location">City center, Podillia, Vyshenka</string>
    <string name="place_11_name">TerraMare restaurants</string>
    <string name="place_11_description">
        A network of trattorias in the main neighborhoods of Vinnytsia. Own salty and sweet
        pastries, a large selection of pizzas and pastas, desserts for every taste.

        76 Kotsyubynskoho Ave
        +380 73 158-00-77

        34 Zodchykh St
        +380 68 136-67-67

        61а Keletska St
        +380 93 787-88-05
        https://terramarenakel.choiceqr.com/

        https://terramare.vn.ua
        https://www.fb.com/terramare.vn
    </string>
    <string name="back_button">back_button</string>
</resources>